Many of you do not seem to grasp that that mindset of socialism is bad is literally just a psyop, a psyop, a psyop, to manufacture consent for these repression and the invasion of countries that are practicing this as if you are not.
The United States practices socialism.
It is completely hypocritical, 100%, and it is a lie to say that the United States is 100% capitalist.
It is not.
Social security has literally social in it.
You can't spell social security without social.
It doesn't want anybody else to actually enact socialism because then it will limit their ability to extract everything from these places.
And Cuba's next, by the way.
Talk about having to deconstruct, having to ask questions, having to disconnect.
Y'all going to learn the song.
Psyop, this is a psyop.
Can't believe nothing.
Because they've been frittin' and they done lied to you.
That's a song I have coming soon.
Let's get it.
Support a real one.
See you.
Deixa you together.
Go away.
Take one.
Start the real one.
If you want to ask questions,uggler.
Change inroyable.
All your eyes.
Save us.
Change inалось.
Take two three.
Click on the next one.